[{"answer": "Well, I hope that we achieve a cease-fire.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 8, "question": "You do believe, Mr. President, that a ground war may be inevitable?", "qSentId": 7}, {"answer": "You know, the likelihood of a cease-fire seems to be increasingly elusive the longer this does drag on, and all through the night, we have been hearing the sound of airstrikes, some of them have actually shook the building that we're standing in.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "He's still saying that it could go either way but what is your sense on the ground about the likely prospects of a cease-fire and how long will the Israelis give it before committing to a possible ground offensive?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "You most certainly do.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "But, Arwa, for those who have never been to the Gaza Strip, it's an extraordinary place in the sense that you've got over 1.5 million people crammed into a relatively small area, haven't you?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, there was also an attempt to introduce a cease- fire.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "How do you see this resolving itself?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, whoever criticized us should suggest an alternative.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "At what stage does it go over the edge and become an unacceptable form of retaliation?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "I think the -- I think critics would say that this particular strategy has proven over the last few years to be an unsuccessful one.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "To take the missile and say what?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Not I guess so, I know that is the case, and we are not going to make a war with Iran.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "If you believe, Mr. President, that Iran is behind a lot of the Hamas terror activity, as you put it, then what action do you intend to take against Iran?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Well, I hope that we shall achieve a cease-fire.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Do you believe, Mr. President, that a ground war may be inevitable?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "I believe that politics and statesmanship is not just a matter of personal relations.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "How would you categorize their relationship from your knowledge?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Is he somebody that you trust and do you believe he should now be wielding, if he can, more authority to try and rein in Hamas?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "We don't put any conditions at all.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "What are you prepared to concede to Hamas if it gets to negotiation?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Two things.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Finally, Mr. President, if there are Palestinians watching this interview who feel helpless, who feel completely poverty-stricken, they have nothing, they see no hope and they now see endless Israeli rockets flying over their heads, perhaps killing relatives and loved ones, what do you say to them to offer proper constructive hope?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's right in the fact that first, of course, Israel has the right to defend itself.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "When you heard Shimon Peres talking, one of the great statesmen of the Middle East, approaching his 90s now, what did you make of what he had to say?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "It is real.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "How real do you think that link is between Iran and Hamas?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, if you -- put your wonderful map up there, you don't have to, but there are all these powder kegs.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Why is the world dangling on this precipice, do you think?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Well, again, that's crisis management.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Well, we don't -- there's no real crime, there's no identified corruption here.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Well, the mood is better, but there's some real serious disagreements on taxes and entitlement reform.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Cease-fire, Alan Dershowitz, is it likely?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "ERSHOWITZ: It's the essential difference between what constitutes a just war and what constitutes an unjust war.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "What is the difference between Hamas murdering innocent women and children in Israel and Israeli missiles murdering innocent Palestinian women and children?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "I think that's a ridiculous and cynical way of talking about what's going on here.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Reza Aslan, your reaction?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "It should not.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Why should Israel have to put up with just endless rockets being fired into civilian areas?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "It should not.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "So what should it do?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "There --", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "But as Shimon Peres said to me, what is the other option?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "There is another option.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "What else do they do?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "I would have said six hours ago if you had asked me that I thought that a cease-fire was quite possible and that the principles were in place for a cease-fire.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "What are they saying?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Let's talk about what is in Israel's benefit.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Well, let's keep in mind the real history here.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "They may win a -- a few small skirmishes, battles even, but they're not going to win the war overtime, are they?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "No, but it is the real -- it is the reality of what's going on here.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Does that justify the rockets?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "I've met them and know them well.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Or is there real oxygen of power terror?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "By the way, let's not pretend that Israel and Hamas are not speaking to each other.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "What's the deal?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Marijuana.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Did I do that?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Well, I probably did.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Did you wake up this morning and have a quick -- you know?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I think some people have more tolerance, you know, for smoking pot than others.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Do you take a lot of it?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Now we can go to Colorado.", "docId": "121119pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "You and Snoop go to Amsterdam, the Mecca of dope, really, and you both have a load of it and then write some music together?", "qSentId": 504}]